Did you know that the world's
first computer bug was an actual
insect that got stuck in the
Harvard Mark II computer back in
1947? This bizarre incident led to
the creation of the term we
used today to describe technical glitches.
In this video, we'll be sharing
some incredible tech facts that will
blow your mind, from the origins
of the internet to the latest
advancements in artificial intelligence. For instance,
the first email was sent in
1971 by Ray Tomlinson, who also
invented the its symbol as a
way to address messages, and the
message was simply a test, reading
courty wipe. The internet as we
know it today was initially called
Arpanet, a project developed in the
1960s by the United States Department
of Defense to create a network
of computers that could communicate with
each other. Another fascinating fact is
that the first smartphone was the
IBM Simon, released in 1994, it
had a touchscreen display and could
send faxes, emails, and even had
a calendar, all of this in
a device that weighed over a
pound. The development of technology has
come a long way since then,
with new advancements being made every
day, from AI-powered robots to
self-driving cars, the future of
tech is exciting and unpredictable. If
you're as fascinated by these tech
facts as we are, be sure
to like and subscribe to our
channel for more content like this,
and hit the notification bell to
stay up to date with the
latest videos. Don't forget to check
out our other videos for more
interesting and lesser-known facts about
the world of technology, and we'll
see you in the next video.